<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string-array name="string_array_banners">
        <item>img_scms</item>
        <item>img_fass</item>
        <item>img_law</item>
        <item>img_library</item>
        <item>img_lakes</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="string_array_titles">
        <item>Computing and Mathematical Sciences</item>
        <item>Arts and Social Sciences</item>
        <item>Law</item>
        <item>University Library</item>
        <item>University Shops and Lakes</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="string_array_content">
        <item>At the School of Computing and Mathematical Sciences we strive to challenge our students and are proud to see them emerge with qualifications that assist them along the path they have planned for their future.\n\nOur aim is to prepare you for a wide variety of careers, equipping you with the skills for academic and professional success. We offer three and four-year degree undergraduate programmes that are based on a strong foundation in the computing and mathematical sciences. The School tries to ensure its papers and qualifications are relevant and up-to-date in what is a rapidly changing technological and social environment.\n\nIn 2016 our School became the first and only New Zealand member of the international group of iSchools - a partnership of the world\'s leading information schools. World-class researchers and facilities underpin unique collaborations within our School, across campus, and with the wider world. These collaborations bring together creative minds, unique technologies, and degree structures tailored to your interests and skills.\n\nA qualification from the University of Waikato in Applied Computing, Computer Science, Mathematics, Data Analytics, Software Engineering or Design can open many doors. Both in New Zealand and overseas, our former students are using their training to make a significant contribution to the world we live in.\n\nWe welcome all of our potential new students, and look forward to seeing you complete your studies and go on to future success in your career.</item>
        <item>The Faculty of Arts and Social Sciences (FASS) was created in 1999 by merging the Schools of Humanities and Social Sciences, and is now one of the larger faculties within the University. It is arguably the most diverse. FASS is made up of three Schools: The School of Arts, the School of Social Sciences and the School of Psychology. Across the faculty we offer over 30 subjects and an enviable range of qualifications. We have more than 140 talented academic staff members, including many with international origins or qualifications. Our research portfolio is recognised nationally and internationally, which reflects the quality of our academic staff.\n\nThe School of Arts prides itself in its innovation in teaching and research. Study the Arts and you learn how to think creatively – at work and at play. The capacity to think clearly, identify issues of significance and articulate a creative response matters.\n\nThe School of Social Sciences is the biggest and most diverse in the Division. Not all of our subjects are conventional ‘social sciences’. Our combination of subjects has the potential to make the School more truly interdisciplinary, multidisciplinary and transdisciplinary than any other comparable grouping in New Zealand.\n\nThe School of Psychology has a strong research profile nationally with a distinctive presence, lively, radical and always changing. Psychology can show us how we think – and how we remember – or forget stuff. It is about feelings and attitudes.</item>
        <item>Founded in 1991, Te Piringa Faculty of Law is now one of New Zealand / Aotearoa’s leading law schools, and is consistently ranked highly internationally and nationally. The Faculty was established upon three core principles: professionalism, biculturalism, and the study of law in context. These founding principles continue to be deeply embedded throughout all our Law programmes, and equip our graduates with a unique and powerful set of skills and strengths. Our students are given the very best grounding in the law, along with a deep understanding of professionalism, biculturalism, and a study of how the law operates in the wider context. Our highly sought after graduates are fully prepared for the complete range of legal and other opportunities – both in Aotearoa / New Zealand as well as abroad.\n\nWe have a diverse and talented community of staff and students, each of whom bring their unique perspectives and experiences to the study and understanding of the law. Along with our high number of Māori students, we also have the highest number of Pasifika law students in the country. This diversity allows for an extraordinarily rich learning environment.\n\nWe have an extensive network of international partners on every continent in the globe, connecting us to leading scholars and law schools in Asia, the Pacific and Australasia, the UK and Europe, North America, South America, and Africa. We prepare our students to be global citizens, and they are able to undertake exchange programmes, study, and work around the world.</item>
        <item>Welcome to the University of Waikato Library - Te Whare Pukapuka o Te Whare Wānanga o Waikato. We combine the best of scholarly tradition with modern facilities and services that support both quiet study and social learning.\n\nAll current members can borrow books, journals, maps and other materials from any of our Libraries in any of these locations - The Library in the Student Centre, Teaching Resources Library, and Tauranga Library (items available may vary depending on the location).\n\nThe University of Waikato has a strong history of digitisation of material that supports research in New Zealand history, and in the development of finding aids for otherwise less-accessible New Zealand content.\n\nThe New Zealand Collection contains several visual collections. We hold selections of photographs, postcards, maps and posters, usually with an emphasis on the Waikato. The following material has been made available online.</item>
        <item>Our main campus is located in the vibrant, multicultural city of Hamilton, with outdoor activities, shopping malls and eateries only a short drive away. On campus, you’ll find a new state-of-the-art Student Centre, sporting facilities, cafes and eateries, car parking, subsidised bus services and more.\n\nBongo Cafe is located in the campus shopping complex. They have a variety of food including hot meals and a ‘select your own’ sushi bar. Open 9am-5pm Monday to Friday.\n\nThe Campus Pharmacy is located in the campus shopping complex. As well as fulfilling prescriptions and selling over-the-counter medicine and first aid, you can also buy stamps, post bags and envelopes. Open 8.30am-5pm Monday to Friday.\n\nKahurangi Cafe is located in the ground floor of the Oranga building, and offers a variety of cafe-style cabinet food and coffee. Open 8am-4pm Monday to Friday.\n\nUni-Mart is located in the campus shopping complex and sells drinks, chips, confectionery and grocery items. Open 8am-6pm Monday to Friday.\n\nThere are three branches of Momento located throughout the campus: in the Waikato Management School, the Student Centre, and in the campus shopping complex. They sell coffee and cafe-style food.</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>